[Music]
I'm Steven I'm the CEO of the oxygen
group afecto is one of the leading
partners in business Central in Belgium
and we mainly focus on wholesale and
distribution companies in Belgium and in
the
Netherlands we are good in in finding
serving and keeping the right uh
customers but we only can grow if you
find enough talented people and that's
why uh the res skill program can help
us the most valuable output so far is
that the rescale program found people
who we never could found ourselves
because they were looking in other areas
uh for people without any Dynamics
experience but with solid uh business
experience in for example warehouse
management or Supply Chain
management for the new BC
it's important that they have an solid
product knowledge of BC AI business
intelligence power apps and so on but
besid of that they also need some
Consulting skills commercial skills
analytical skills and uh what I really
like about the rescale program is that
uh the program helps us on both sides as
well on the product side as on the
Consulting
side the people we have hired via the
program are very
enthusiastic they are eager to learn and
they were rapidly integrated in our
whole
team and after a few weeks we involved
them in our existing customer projects
they had a positive impact and they are
already buildable after two or three
months for at least
50% other pars should join the res skill
program to get the same good results as
we do and of course to enlarge the
community of BC Talent